CONTACT ME AT

• i-14/1 islamabad
0315-5896001

asharibkamal1@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/asharib-kamal1/

SKILLS SUMMARY

Dot Net Developer

Software Development

C# Programming

ERP)Enterprise Resource Planning)

Microsoft SQL Server

VB.NET, .NET core, .NET5

- Wordpress Development
- Affiliate Marketing

ASHARIB KAMAL

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | . NET

PERSONAL PROFILE

Lightning-fast, exacting .NET developer with 4+ years of experience. Skilled in C#, ASP.NET, VB.Net, Dot Net(5,6,7), MVC. Seeking a position at a software company. As a Developer at Daewoo Express Pakistan Private Ltd, worked on 15+ projects for Desktop and Web Applications. Developed and maintained over 10+ .NET Web Applications with 100% client satisfaction.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deputy Manager Dot NET Developer

Daewoo Express PVT.Ltd | JAN 2023 - Present

As a Dot Net Developer at Daewoo Express, I have been working with clients to deliver high-quality enterprise software solutions and web and Desktop Applications using .NET 6, ASP.NET MVC, and Web Forms.

I have been collaborating with the team to ensure that the software meets the client's requirements and is delivered on time.

<u>Skills</u>: C#, .NET Framework · JavaScript · AJAX - JQuery · SQL - Rest Api's - .NET (5,6).

Senior Software Developer

Carbon8 PVT.Ltd | Feb 2022 - december 2022

As a Dot Net Developer at Carbon8, I have been working on Existing Desktop Applications adding new modules, and resolving, testing, and deploying the application.

<u>Skills</u>: C# \cdot , VB.NET, .NET Framework \cdot Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) \cdot SQL Language MSSQL Server, Windows Form. Dot NET Core

Junior Software Developer (2 Years)

Cloud Support | Jan 2019 - Dec 2020

- As a Junior Dot Net Developer at Cloud Support, I have been working with a Local-based client to deliver high-quality enterprise software solutions (ERP), Web Applications using Web Forms, JavaScript, jQuery, and Ajax SQL server.
- Create RDLC and Crystal Report for ERP software like Trail Balance, General Ledger, Daily cash book, Purchase invoice, etc
- Develop Web Application ERP for Floor Mills, Steel Mills ad different companies.
- use C# programming and Dot net 3.2 Framework and Microsoft SQL Server as a Database.

MY PROJECTS

Attendance Portal | .NET 6 | API's | Javascript | SQL

Daewoo Attendance Portal | JUNE 2023 - Present

As a Dot Net Developer at Daewoo Express, I have Developed the Daewoo Attendance Portal from Scratch.

Skills: Rest Api's, .net 6, Javascript, Ajax , SQL Server

Call Center (CRM) | .Net 6 | Javascript | Ajax | SQL

Daewoo Fastex CRM | Feb 2022 - december 2022

As a Dot Net Developer at Daewoo Express, I have Developed Daewoo CRM Portal from Scratch using .NET 6, JavaScript, Ajax, and SQL.

modules:

- Tracking Detail
- Ticket Generate against tracking id
- Create a ticket and send a message to the complainer
- Ticket Update

ERP SYSTEM | Web Forms | ASP.NET | SQL Server

ERP System for Floor Mills | Jan 2019 - oct 2020

Working on ERP Software Cloud-Based Web Application Technology used ASP.net, C#, JavaScript, Jquery, and Database MSSQL.

Create RDLC Report for ERP software like Trail Balance, General Ledger, Daily cash book, Purchase invoice, etc. Develop and maintain ERP systems and solve issues using ASp.Net and SQL Server as databases. use Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, and c# programming.

EDUCATION

BS(Hons) | Computer Science

University of Wah | Jan 2013 - oct 2017

I have completed my graduation from the university of wah (Wahcantt).

FSC | Pre- Engineering

Jinnah College of Commerce | Feb 2011 - Jan 2013

• I have done my intermediate from Jinnah college of commerce.

Matric | Science

IMCB F-8/4 Islamabad | Jan 2008 - oct 2010

I have completed my Matric from the IMCB F-8/4 Islamabad.

COURSES

Wordpress

Digiskills | JUL 2022 - OCT 2022

• I have completed my wordpress course from digiskills learn wordpress development php mysql.

Digital Marketing

Google Digital Garage | Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

• I have completed my Digital Marketing Course from Google

Affiliate Marketing

Digiskills | JULL 2022 - OCT 2022

I have completed my Affiliate Marketing course from digiskills learn Marketing, SEO, Advertising, Rank Website etc.

Web Development

Digiskills | Mar 2023 - May 2023

I have completed my Web Development course from Digiskills learning HTML, CSS, JavaSCript, and PHP.